<resources>
    <string-array name="muted_seasonal_wisdom_45">
        <item>1. The heat of summer brings the laziness of the soul.</item>
        <item>2. Summer is the time for swimming, sunbathing, and relaxation.</item>
        <item>3. The summer sun can be both a blessing and a curse.</item>
        <item>4. The joy of summer is in its long, lazy days.</item>
        <item>5. Summer is the season for outdoor adventures and exploration.</item>
        <item>6. In the summer, the world is full of vibrant colors and sweet scents.</item>
        <item>7. The summer heat can be unbearable, but it always comes to an end.</item>
        <item>8. Summer is the season for ice cream, lemonade, and picnics.</item>
        <item>9. The beauty of summer lies in its simplicity and carefree spirit.</item>
        <item>10. Summer is a time to reconnect with nature and find inner peace.</item>
        <item>11. The summer sky is a canvas of endless possibilities and dreams.</item>
        <item>12. The warmth of summer can melt even the coldest heart.</item>
        <item>13. Summer is a time for new beginnings and fresh starts.</item>
        <item>14. In the summer, time slows down and life feels more enjoyable.</item>
        <item>15. The beauty of summer is in its ability to bring people together.</item>
        <item>16. Summer is the season for love, laughter, and joy.</item>
        <item>17. The heat of summer can be tamed with a cool breeze and shade.</item>
        <item>18. Summer is a time to let go of worries and live in the moment.</item>
        <item>19. The summer sun brings energy and vitality to everything it touches.</item>
        <item>20. In the summer, life is a never-ending adventure waiting to be explored.</item>
        <item>21. Summer is the season for growth, both physically and spiritually.</item>
        <item>22. The beauty of summer is in its simplicity and natural beauty.</item>
        <item>23. Summer is a time to embrace change and take risks.</item>
        <item>24. In the summer, the world is full of endless possibilities and opportunities.</item>
        <item>25. The joy of summer is in its ability to bring happiness to the heart.</item>
        <item>26. Summer is a time to let loose and have fun.</item>
        <item>27. The summer sun brings warmth and comfort to the soul.</item>
        <item>28. In the summer, the world is full of beauty and wonder.</item>
        <item>29. Summer is the season for relaxation, rejuvenation, and self-care.</item>
        <item>30. The beauty of summer is in its ability to inspire creativity and imagination.</item>
        <item>31. Summer is a time to explore new places and try new things.</item>
        <item>32. In the summer, the world is full of adventure and excitement.</item>
        <item>33. Summer is the season for growth, change, and transformation.</item>
        <item>34. The joy of summer is in its ability to bring people happiness and joy.</item>
        <item>35. Summer is a time to connect with nature and appreciate its beauty.</item>
        <item>36. The beauty of summer is in its simplicity and peacefulness.</item>
        <item>37. Summer is a time to slow down and enjoy the simple things in life.</item>
        <item>38. In the summer, the world is full of magic and wonder.</item>
        <item>39. Summer is the season for healing, both physically and emotionally.</item>
        <item>40. The joy of summer is in its ability to bring people together and create memories.</item>
        <item>41. Summer is a time to reflect on the past and plan for the future.</item>
        <item>42. The beauty of summer is in its ability to nourish the soul and replenish the spirit.</item>
        <item>43. Summer is a time to let go of stress and embrace relaxation.</item>
        <item>44. In the summer, the world is full of beauty and inspiration.</item>
        <item>45. Summer is the season for gratitude and appreciation.</item>
        <item>46. The joy of summer is in its ability to make people feel alive and vibrant.</item>
        <item>47. Summer is a time to be present in the moment and appreciate the simple things in life.</item>
        <item>48. The beauty of summer is in its ability to inspire hope and optimism.</item>
        <item>49. Summer is a time to embrace change and growth.</item>
        <item>50. In the summer, the world is full of endless possibilities and opportunities for growth and transformation.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>